JAVIER PEREZ

ORLANDO, FL 32837

Phone: (786) 656-5650 | Email: Japb1998@gmail.com LinkedIn: _linkedin.com/in/javier-perez-a0b0a81b3 | GitHub: https://github.com/japb1998 |

Portfolio: https://japb1998.github.io/NewPortfolio/

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer with experience in customer service, strengths in front-end functionality and backend logic, strong problem-solving skills with the ability to combine creativity with logic. Stellar communication skills with ability to connect with people and provide excellent service.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL

Technologies: React.js,Redux,GitHub,

MongoDB, MySQL, JQuery, Axios, MaterializeCss, GraphQL, JSON.

PROJECTS

Hello World Social Media | https://helloworld-social-app.netlify.app

- Social Media app develop on MERN Stack
- https://github.com/japb1998/socialMediaApp
- JavaScript , CSS3, HTML5, ReactJS, GraphQL, Apollo, MongoDB

Pandora |https://pandora-e-commerce.herokuapp.com/

- E-commerce website with user login functionality
- https://github.com/japb1998/E-Commerce-Site
- JavaScript , CSS3, MongoDB, ReactJS

•

Dinner&Movies |https://japb1998.github.io/1_GroupProyect/

- Random movie selector with the genres you pick with the right recipes to have a perfect movie night
- https://github.com/japb1998/1 GroupProyect
- JavaScript , CSS3,HTML

EXPERIENCE

2U/Trilogy Senior Learning Assistant for FSF 2021 – Current

Remote

Assist students during their learning process, assist Learning assistants with complicated questions, curriculum issues and schedules while making sure students have the best possible experience.

Assist students during their learning process, code challenges and projects related to the full stack MERN software development program.

Grading Team 2U/Trilogy

2021 -Current

Remote

Correcting and grading students' assignments each week, giving specific details of how the code could be better or more efficient, and providing adequate documentation.

UbreaklFix

Technician-Manager 2018 – 2019

Deerfield,FL

Read and interpret technical documentation in order to accurately configure equipment. Performed complete phone erasures and factory resets, debugged problems and refurbished devices. Completed new OS installations on phones, tablets and laptops.

Improved operations by working with team members and customers to find workable solutions. Improved profit margins by streamlining operations and workflow and negotiating competitive vendor contracts

EDUCATION

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development MERN Stack – University of Central Florida Orlando, FL

Private Pilot – AAWFT with License at INAC

Caracas, Venezuela

Some College, Mechanical Engineer – Simon Bolivar University

Caracas, Venezuela